Guide to the William L. Taylor papers, 1954-2009 MS2287
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1954-2003; Series 3; 24.5 Linear Feet
  - Center for National Policy Review, Series 3 Subseries 4
    - School desegregation -- Types of Discrimination Found by Federal District Courts in Northern Desegregation Cases, undated; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - School desegregation -- WLT [William L. Taylor's] School Desegregation 1976: Does Success Lead to Failure?, Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Title IX -- Prohibition of Sex Discrimination, 1972-1974; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - U.S. v. Board of School Commissioners of the City of Indianapolis, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Citizens' Commission on Civil Rights, Series 3 Subseries 5
    - Affirmative Action, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Action -- ACE, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Affirmative Action -- Adarand, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Affirmative Action -- Black Enterprise, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action -- briefings [1 of 2], undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Affirmative Action -- briefings [2 of 2], undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Affirmative Action -- business survey, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - [Affirmative Action] resource -- 2nd issue consents, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - [Affirmative Action] resource #3, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - [Affirmative Action] resource -- response letters, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Affirmative Action -- California, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Action -- case law [1 of 2], undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Affirmative Action -- case law [2 of 2], undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Affirmative Action -- charts and graphs, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Action -- class, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Affirmative Action -- Congress, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Affirmative Action -- corporate interviews, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action -- edit memo, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - CCCR Affirmative Action final report, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Affirmative Action -- higher education interviews, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Affirmative Action -- Higher Education VNR, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Affirmative Action -- House hearing, 1995 March 24; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Action -- House hearing, 1995 April 3; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - [Affirmative Action] -- House hearing, Employer/Employee Subcommittee, 1995 May 2; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - [Affirmative Action] -- House hearing, OFCCP, 1995 June 21; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - [Affirmative Action] -- House hearing, Civil Rights Division, 1995 July 20; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - [Affirmative Action] -- House hearing, Subcommittee on the Constitution, Dole-Canady Bill, 1995 December 7; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - [Affirmative Action] -- House hearing, Employer/Employee Relations, OFCCP/HR 2128, 1996 February 29; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Affirmative Action -- Looseleaf, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Affirmative Action -- Looseleaf backup, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Affirmative Action -- miscellaneous media, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Affirmative Action -- Op-ed, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Affirmative Action -- Press conference, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Affirmative Action -- Project notes, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Affirmative Action -- Rawlings interview, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Affirmative Action -- Research, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Action -- Senate hearing, 1995 June 15; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Affirmative Action -- Senate hearing, 1995 September 7; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Affirmative Action -- Senate hearing, 1995 October 23; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action -- Senate Labor and Human Resources hearing, 1996 April 30; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Affirmative Action -- Senate Judiciary Committee hearing, 1996 April 30; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Affirmative Action -- State Agency Survey, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Affirmative Action -- VNR, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Affirmative Action -- Young interview, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Citizens Commission Founding Matching Proposal, undated; Series 2 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - CCCR board meeting, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - CCCR conference, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - CCCR meeting, 1983; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - CCCR proposal correspondence, 2002; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - CCCR survey on NCLB, 2005; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Clark Foundation Meeting, 1981 October 22; Series 2 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Commission meeting, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - NCTQ-CCCR advisory board meeting, 2005; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - OFCCP -- misc., undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - OFCCP -- enforcement data, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - OFCCP -- glass ceiling, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - OFCCP -- impact of affirmative action, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - OFCCP -- talking points, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - OFCCP -- consent decrees, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - OFCCP -- EVE/EPIC Awards, undated; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Survey of Human Rights Agencies [1 of 5], 1995; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Survey of Human Rights Agencies [2 of 5], 1995; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Survey of Human Rights Agencies [3 of 5], 1995; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Survey of Human Rights Agencies [4 of 5], 1995; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Survey of Human Rights Agencies [5 of 5], 1995; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, Series 3 Subseries 6
    - ADA Disability Bill, 1989; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Affordable housing, 1989; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Department of Education legislative proposals, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - "ED-FLEX" legislation, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - ESEA [Elementary and Secondary Education Act], 1999-2000; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - ESEA [Elementary and Secondary Education Act] Conference Report Text [1 of 2], 2001; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - ESEA [Elementary and Secondary Education Act] Conference Report Text [2 of 2], 2001; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - ESEA [Elementary and Secondary Education Act] -- legislative, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - ESEA [Elementary and Secondary Education Act] Policy Brief #1 -- Portability vs. Right to Transfer from Failing Schools, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - ESEA [Elementary and Secondary Education Act] Policy Brief #2 -- Accountability and Student Achievement Gains, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - ESEA [Elementary and Secondary Education Act] Policy Brief #3, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - ESEA [Elementary and Secondary Education Act] Policy Brief #4 -- AYP Analysis and Recommendations, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - ESEA [Elementary and Secondary Education Act] reauthorization, 1998-2000; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - ESEA [Elementary and Secondary Education Act] reauthorization, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - [ESEA reauthorization] Fact sheet originals, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - [ESEA reauthorization] Press release originals, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Fact sheet -- Accountability, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Fact sheet -- Myths and realities, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Fact sheet -- Portability, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Fact sheet -- Reauthorization, Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Fact sheet -- Teacher quality, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - HR 1995 Teacher Empowerment Act, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Joint Project Information LCCR/CCCR, 2000 May 5; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - LCCR, 1973-1981; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - LCCR Board meeting, 2005 December 5; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - LCCR Education Task Force, 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - LCCR Education Fund Board of Directors meeting, 2006 March 31; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - LCCR Justice Department report, 1982; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - LCCR Objectives for Reauthorization of ESEA, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - LCCR Social Security Conference, Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - LCCR Title I issues, Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - LCCREF board meeting, 2007; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Press release -- Future of Title I, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - "Straight As" legislation, undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Liddell v. Board of Education of the City of St. Louis, Series 3 Subseries 7
    - Board of Education of the City of St. Louis v. The State of Missouri, Brief of Appellee, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 12)
    - Board of Education of the City of St. Louis v. The State of Missouri, Brief of Appellee, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 13)
    - Board of Education of the City of St. Louis v. State of Missouri, Reply Brief of Appellee, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 1)
    - Board of Education of the City of St. Louis v. The State of Missouri, Appendix to Brief of Appellee, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Binder 1)
    - Board of Education of the City of St. Louis v. The State of Missouri, Reply Brief of Appellee, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Binder 2)
    - Board of Education of the City of St. Louis v. Missouri National Education Association, Appellant Missouri NEA's Reply Brief, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Binder 5)
    - Board of Education of the City of St. Louis v. The State of Missouri, Reply Brief of Appellant Board of Education, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Binder 9)
    - Board of Education of the City of St. Louis v. The State of Missouri, Brief of Appellee St. Louis Career Education District, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Binder 10)
    - Board of Education of the City of St. Louis v. The State of Missouri, Appellee Special School District's Brief, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Binder 11)
    - Board of Education of the City of St. Louis v. The State of Missouri, Brief of Appellant Board of Education of the City of St. Louis, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Binder 12)
    - Craton Liddell v. Board of Education, 1980; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Craton Liddell v. The Special School District, Reply Brief of Certain St. Louis County School Districts as Appellants, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 9)
    - Craton Liddell v. The Special School District, Reply Brief of Certain St. Louis County School Districts as Appellants, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 10)
    - Craton Liddell v. The Special School District, Reply Brief of Certain St. Louis County School Districts as Appellants, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 11)
    - Finding of Facts, Conclusions of Law and Order, 1983; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Hornbeck v. Somerset County Board, 1983; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Jenkins/Benson brief, 1996 October; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Liddell, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Liddell, 1992-1995; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Liddell documents [1 of 3], 1983; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Liddell documents [2 of 3], 1983; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Liddell documents [3 of 3], 1983; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Liddell/Amicus Curiae briefs -- 8th Circuit, 1983; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Liddell Briefs on Relevance of Evidence, 1995 November; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Liddell CED, enrollment, 1996 November; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Liddell/City Board's Comprehensive Assessment Motion and Replies, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Liddell/EMAC evaluation and information, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Liddell/final Caldwell motions, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Liddell/financing of plan, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Liddell/funding and NAACP, Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Liddell/housing, 1995-1996; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Liddell/Joint Motion for Judgment, 1983; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Liddell/Leonard Stevens, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Liddell/material for deposition, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Liddell material -- hearing, 1995 October 11; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Liddell materials and related articles, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Liddell Memorandum and Order, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Liddell/Motion to Exclude Expert Testimony, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Liddell/Motion of Plaintiffs to Clarify and Certify, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Liddell notes, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Liddell/notes at trial, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Liddell/Orfield, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Liddell/prehearing briefs, 1996 February; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Liddell/Puma, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Liddell/Qs and As for Uchitelle and Dixon, 1996 March; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Liddell/Rockwood, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Liddell/school research, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Liddell/Special School District appeal, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Liddell/special education, 1983; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Liddell/State and CSD opposition to PS motion of January 18, 1996, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Liddell/State urban policy legislation, 1994-1995; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Liddell/Statements of Claims and Defenses, 1995 September; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Liddell/Stay -- 8th Circuit, 1983 August; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Liddell/Stringfield and Herman, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Liddell/Trent, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Liddell trial outline, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Liddell outgoing correspondence, 1997 January-March; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Liddell incoming correspondence, 1997 October-December; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Michael C. Liddell v. The Special School District, Brief for the United States as Appellee, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 2)
    - Michael C. Liddell v. The Board of Education of the City of St. Louis, Brief of State of Missouri Appellants, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 3)
    - Michael C. Liddell v. The Board of Education of the City of St. Louis, Appendix of State of Missouri Appellants, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 4)
    - Michael C. Liddell v. The Special School District, Appellant SSD's Brief, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 5)
    - Michael C. Liddell v. The Special School District, Brief for the United States as Appellee, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 6)
    - Michael C. Liddell v. The Special School District, Reply Brief of State of Missouri Appellants, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 7)
    - Michael C. Liddell v. The Special School District, Reply Brief of State of Missouri Appellants, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 60, Binder 8)
    - Michael C. Liddell v. The Special School District, Brief of Appellee St. Louis Career Education District, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Binder 6)
    - Michael C. Liddell v. The Special School District, Appellant SSD's Reply Brief, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Binder 7)
    - Michael C. Liddell v. The Board of Education of the City of St. Louis, Brief of the Appellees, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Binder 3)
    - Michael C. Liddell v. The Board of Education of the City of St. Louis, Brief of the Appellees, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Binder 4)
    - Michael C. Liddell v. The Special School District, Appellant SSD's Reply Brief, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Binder 8)
    - Racial Enrollment Data, 1972-1973; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - St. Louis test scores, 1990-1994; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - State of Missouri v. Craton Liddell -- 8th Circuit, undated; Series 3 Subseries 7 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Liddell v. Board of Education, Series 3 Subseries (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - General, Series 3 Subseries 8
    - Abbott v. Burke, New Jersey, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 111, Folder 21)
    - Abbott v. Burke, New Jersey, 1990 June 16; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 111, Folder 22)
    - Abbott v. Burke, Plaintiff's brief on appeal to New Jersey Supreme Court, 1989 June 16; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 111, Folder 20)
    - Abbott v. Burke, T. Corcoran testimony, undated; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Info from M. Morheuser re: data on SF issues and analysis of Abbott, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Abraham Lincoln High School, 1946-1948; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - ADA Lawyers Committee materials, 1970-1971; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - AFSC reports on school desegregation and equal opportunity in housing, 1965-1967; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Alliance for Justice/Current Working, 1980; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Alliance for Justice/Regulatory Project, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Alliance for Justice/Current Working, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Alliance for Justice/Current Working, 1982-1984; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Alliance for Justice/Current Working, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Alliance for Justice lunch, Taylor honoree, 1986 May 12; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - [Americans for Democratic Action] ADA Legislative Newsletters and Testimony, 1959; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Armour v. Nix, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Baltimore Law Review on MD education, undated; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Bannockburn -- Authorities, undated; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Bannockburn appeal -- court papers, 1971-72; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Betts decision, 1989; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Board of Education, Levittown v. Nyquist, undated; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn College Vanguard, 1998; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Bush report -- printing and publishing info, Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - California school finance and educational data, undated; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Certificates, transcripts, and letters of recommendation, 1955-1982; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Chapter I Commission -- fiscal issues, 1992-1993; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Civil rights -- President John F. Kennedy, 1960; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Civil rights attorneys' fees, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Commissioners' bios, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Congratulatory notes re: piece in New York Review of Books, 2005 October; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Containment of Minority Groups through Housing, undated; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Council for Better Education v. Wilkinson (Kentucky case), undated; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - CR Act 1991 Retroactivity briefs, Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Data research file -- school finance project, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Detroit decentralization, 1969; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - DMP/Rand materials, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Bill Doyle's memo on Alabama case, undated; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Education bill -- Muskie, 1972; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Education Coalition, 1978; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Education -- Mondale committee, WT [William Taylor] consultant, 1970; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Education writers, 1981-1982; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Employer sanctions, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Employer sanctions -- legislation, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Employment cases, 1989; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Employment cases -- Haynes, Jett, Patterson, etc., undated; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Fair Chance Act -- Outline of Report, 1990 July; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Fair Chance Act -- proposal and budget, Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Fair Chance Act -- Testimony by Bert C. Combs, Subcommittee on Elementary, Secondary, and Vocational Education, undated; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Federal education legislation, 1989; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - FWCS [Fort Wayne Community Schools] Board: PTA busing survey, 1986; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - FWCS stats and building data -- MHRC, undated; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Fort Wayne hospitals questionnaire, 1967; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Fort Wayne housing, undated; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Fort Wayne housing -- Relocation Report, 1970; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Fort Wayne Optional Areas, 1968; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Fort Wayne school site selection, 1968; Series 3 Subseries 8 (Box 66, Folder 7)